<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="hello">Hello World, LoadCube!</string>
    <string name="app_name">Rubiks Cube Solver</string>
    <string name="actionbar_activity_not_found">Failed to open intent...</string>
    <string name="strInsTitle">Instructions</string>
    <string name="strInstructions">For best results start by placing your cube on a flat surface. The first side you will have to take is the front. Match up the box that says TL with the top left corner of the cube, then press the camera button to take the picture. IMPORTANT : Remember which side is the FRONT, and which side was UP. This is the orientation of the cube that the solution will start out with. Then you will be asked to move onto the RIGHT. Simply turn the cube left so that the RIGHT side is not facing upwards. The UP face should still be the same. Take the picture than continue. Do this for the BACK then LEFT sides. Now orient the cube to the way you just started. Turn the cube down so that you are now looking at the UP face, and then take the picture. Then simarally do the same for the DOWN face. Inbetween these steps you will have the chance to make sure all colors are correct. You can start over at any time by clicking the menu button, then clicking start over. Once you are done the solution will appear on screen. The solution will be save automatically and you will can view all previous solutions by clicking the history button below. Have Fun!</string>
    <string name="front">front</string>
    <string name="right">right</string>
    <string name="back">back</string>
    <string name="left">left</string>
    <string name="up">up</string>
    <string name="down">down</string>
    <string name="goHome">Start Over</string>
    <string name="deleteSol">Delete Solution</string>
    <string name="tryAgain">Try Again</string>
    <string name="nextFace">Next Face</string>
    <string name="solveCube">Solve</string>
    <string name="invalidCube">This cube is invalid/cannot be solved.</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="aboutText">"By: DroidTools &lt;droidtools@gmail.com&gt;
    
Native C Solver by Eric Dietz &lt;http://www.wrongway.org>

Animated Cube by Josef Jelinek &lt;http://software.rubikscube.info/AnimCube/&gt; 

Source Code available at &lt;https://github.com/nemothekid/Android-Rubik-s-Cube-Solver&gt;"</string>
    <string name="tooColors">There are more than 6 colors on this cube. Please make sure each color on this face has the same color number (that is also identical to the color number of the same color on other faces).</string>
    <string name="checkColors">The ungrouped colors column must be cleared and each face must have atleast on facelet color.</string>
    <string name="actionTitle">"Rubik's Cube Solver"</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="prev">Prev</string>
    <string name="selectSimilar">Please group each facelet by color. Press a facelet from either side to move it to the grouped side or ungrouped side.</string>
    <string name="insStep1">First take a picture of the first face of the cube, then on the next page, make sure all the colors match up. You can select a facelet to change its color.</string>
    <string name="insStep2">Turn the entire cube left so that you are looking at the right face from the front.</string>
    <string name="insStep3">Turn the entire cube left so that you are looking at the back face from the front.</string>
    <string name="insStep4">Turn the entire cube left so that you are looking at the left face from the front.</string>
    <string name="insStep5">Turn the entire cube left, then rotate it up. Make sure you are looking at the up face such that the down face is the front face.</string>
    <string name="insStep6">Turn the entire cube down so that you are looking at the down face from the front. Take the final picture and press solve.</string>
    <string name="insStep7">Solve!</string>
</resources>
